M Huzaifa Imran

Software Engineer

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Python, Scrapy, React.js, Node.js, PHP, Laravel, C++, Java, and Data Engineering. Strong engineering professional with a bachelor's Degree In Computer Science.



Lahore

3 4 3

mhuzaifaimran88@gmail.com

03204522924



Lahore, Pakistan



EDUCATION

F.S.C(Pre-Engineering) Punjab Group Of Colleges

07/2016 - 04/2018

Courses

MathematicsChemistry

BsCs

Superior University, Lahore

08/2018 - 04/2022

Main Courses

- Advance Web and Mobile Development
- Computer Architecture
- Java OOP
- Advanced Programming Language
- Mobile Application Development

- Design Analysis Algorithms
- Software Engineering
- Data Structures and Algorithm
- Digital Logical and Designing
- Artificial intelligence

EXPERIENCE

WordPress Deveoper RsSoft

04/2020 - 08/2020

Associate Software Engineer

Innova

02/2021 - 11/2021

Backend Developer

Enrichers Pvt. Ltd

12/2021 - Present

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

E-Commerce Website

 Developed A fully Functioned E-Commerce Website using React.js for the front-end and Node.js for backend with database Mongoose Db (Mern-Stack Project)

CodeMobo

 Developed A Companies Portfolio Website using Mern-Stack Technology. React.js for frontend and Node.js for backend with database Mongoose Db

Pharmacy Billing System

 Developed A Pharmacy Management System in C++ and Mobile Application in Java Language for a Local Area Pharmacy

Quiz Generating app

 Developed A quiz generating app with a proper marketing strategy for mah own purpose

Online Ticketing System

Java Semester Project

ACHIVEMENTS

Istanbul Youth Summit 2021 (01/2022 - 01/2022)

COV-ROB was selected in top 40 projects all over the world in IYS'21

National Idea Bank (07/2021 - 07/2021)

COV-ROB is the finalist of National Idea Bank

Queens Entrepreneurs Competition, Canada (02/2022 - 02/2022)

National Entrepreneurship Summit (2021)

Punjab Information Technology Board

Runner Up of Superior Startup Championship (2021)

Chaudhry Muhammad Akram Center For Entrepreneurship